Tyler Conn

UX Designer Atlanta, GA

Portfolio

tylerconn.me

Contact

tyler@tylerconn.me 864.525.3214 linkedin.com/in/tylerconn

Skills

Design Thinking

Wireframes

User Flow Creation

User Interviews

Persona Creation

Prototyping

Feature Prioritization

Storyboarding

Usability Testing

Typography

Color Theory

Iconography

HTML/CSS

iQuery

GitHub

Bootstrap

Visual Studio Code

Figma/Adobe XD

Responsive Design

Atomic Design

Interaction Design

PROJECTS

UX Design Project

tylerconn.me/energy-dept

The goal of this project was to evaluate an existing government website, identify any problems with the user experience, and redesign the website to address these problems. As this was a solo project, I performed all aspects of the project from user research and persona creation to defining the problem, ideating, prototyping, and testing.

Web Design/Development Project

tylerconn.me/room-shui

In this project, I was tasked to work with a team in order to identify a problem that could be solved with a web solution, and research, design, and develop the solution to the problem. My primary contributions included developing a research plan, and creating both a low-fidelity and later high-fidelity prototype in Figma.

EXPERIENCE

Equifax Jul 2018 - Present

Revenue Accounting Manager

- Designed and implemented a web app to automate our contract reporting process
- · Reviewed new contracts and determined the appropriate revenue plan
- Managed the monthly revenue accounting process for several businesses
- · Developed new accounting processes for several acquired companies

Equifax Nov 2018 - Mar 2019

Interim Director of Corporate Accounting

- Oversaw the work of local and international accounting teams to complete monthly corporate accounting processes accurately and within required timeframes
- Coordinated with key stakeholders in multiple departments across the organization to inform them of accounting decisions and ensure there was agreement

EY Sep 2015 - Jul 2018

Senior Auditor

- Led hundreds of interviews with process owners to document client's process flow and identify any deficiencies
- Planned testing procedures and coordinated with clients and various internal teams to meet deadlines

EDUCATION

Georgia Institute of Technology

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

Certificate - UX/UI Design

Bob Jones University

Sep 2011 - May 2015

Bachelors of Science - Accounting

- · Minor in Spanish, with studies abroad in Spain
- · Graduated magna cum laude